const vocab = [
    {
        "question": "Hello",
        "answer": "你好 (nǐ hǎo)",
    },
    {
        "question": "Goodbye",
        "answer": "再見 (zàijiàn)",
    },
    {
        "question": "School",
        "answer": "學校 (xuéxiào)",
    },
    {
        "question": "Animal",
        "answer": "動物 (dòng wù)",
    },
    {
        "question": "Body",
        "answer": "身体 (shēn tǐ)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Body",
        "answer": "身体 (shēn tǐ)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Teacher",
        "answer": "老師 (lǎoshī)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Dog",
        "answer": "狗 (gǒu)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Cake",
        "answer": "蛋糕 (dàngāo)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Congratulations",
        "answer": "恭喜你 (gōng xǐ nǐ)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Excited",
        "answer": "興奮 (xīngfèn)",
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Hungry",
        "answer": "餓 (è)",
    }, 
];

export default vocab;